Guide to the William A. Speck Collection of Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits, Series I; 5; (12 boxes)
  - "H"
    - Heinse, Johann Jakob Wilhelm, 1749-1803 (Box 6, Folder ++)
    - Henke, Heinrich Philipp Konrad, 1752-1809 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Hensel, Wilhelm, 1794-1861 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Herder, Johann Gottfried von, 1744-1803 (Box 6, Folder ++)
    - Herder, Frau Maria Caroline Flachsland von, 1750-1809 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Herder, Siegmund August Wolfgang, Freiherr von, 1776-1838 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Hermann, Christian Gottfried, 1743-1813 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Hermes, Johann Timotheus, 1738-1821 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Herzlieb, Christian Friedrick Karl, 1760-1794 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Hessen-Darmstadt, Henriette Christine Caroline Louise, Landgräfin von, 1721-1774 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Heygendorf, Frau Henriette Caroline Friederike Jagemann von, 1777-1848 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Heyne, Christian Gottlob, 1729-1812 (Box 6, Folder ++)
    - Hiller, Ferdinand, 1811-1885 (Box 6, Folder +)
    - Hiller, Johann Adam, 1728-1804 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Hilpert (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Himly, Karl Gustav & Jena, 1772-1837 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Himmel, Friedrich Heinrich, 1765-1819 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hirt, Aloys Ludwig, 1759-1839 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hölderlin, Friedrich, 1770-1843 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hölty, Ludwig Heinrich Christoph, 1748-1776 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Höpfner, Ludwig Julius Friederich, 1743-1797 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Holtei, Karl von, 1798-1880 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hoffman, Ernst Theodor Amadeus, 1776-1822 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Houwald, Ernst Christoph, Freiherr von, 1778-1845 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Huber, Ludwig Ferdinand, 1764-1804 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Huber, Frau Marie Therese Forster Heyne, 1764-1829 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Huber, Michel, 1727-1804 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Huck (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hüsgen (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hufeland, Christoph Wilhelm, 1762-1836 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hugo, Gustav, 1764-1844 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Humboldt, Alexander, Freiherr von, 1769-1859 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Humboldt, Wilhelm, Freiherr von, 1767-1835 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Humboldt - Family (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Hummel, Johann Nepomuk, 1778-1837 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Hunt, Leigh, 1784-1859 (Box 7, Folder +)
  - "I"
    - Iffland, August Wilhelm, 1759-1814 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Imhoff - Family (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Iselin (Box 7, Folder +)
  - "J"
    - Jacobi, Friedrich Heinrich, 1743-1819 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Jacobi, Johann Georg, 1740-1814 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Jacobi, Frau Helene Elisabeth von Clermont, 1743-1784 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Jacobi - Family (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Jagemann, Christian Joseph, 1735-1804 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Jagemann, Ferdinand Karl Christian, 1780-1820 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Jagemann, Karl Wilhelm, 1747-1772 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Joseph Anton Johann, archduke of Austria, 1776-1847 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Joseph II, emperor of Germany, 1741-1790 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Juel, Jens, 1745-1802 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Juncker, Justus, 1703-1767 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Jung-Stilling, Johann Heinrich, 1740-1817 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Junot, Frau Caroline Friedrike Luise Schiller, 1799-1850 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Junot, Felix, 1839-1844 (Box 7, Folder +)
  - "K"
    - Kalb, Frau Charlotte Sophia Juliane Marschalk von Ostheim von, 1761-1843 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Kalb, Jahann August Alexander von, 1747-1814 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kalb, Karl Alexander von, 1712-1793 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kalckreuth, Friedrich Adolf, Graf von, 1737-1818 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kanne, Frau Anne Katharine Schönkopf, 1746-1810 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Kapodistrias, Ioannes Antonios, Komes, 1776-1831 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Karl Alexander, Grand Duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1818-1901 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Karl August, Grand Duke of Saxe-Wiemar-Eisenach, 1757-1828 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Karl Eugen, duke of Würtemberg, 1728-1793 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Karl Friedrich, Grand Duke of Baden, 1728-1811 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Karl Friedrich, Grand Duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1783-1853 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Karl Theodor, Kurfürst von Bayern, 1724-1799 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Karl Wilhelm Ferdinand, Duke of Brunswick and Lüneburg, 1735-1806 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Karschin, Frau Anna Luisa Dürbach Hirsekorn, 1722-1791 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kauffmann, Angelica, 1741-1807 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kaulbach, Wilhelm von, 1805-1876 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kayser, Philipp Christoph, 1755-1823 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kersting, Friedrich Georg, 1783-1847 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kestner - Family (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kestner, Frau Charlotte Buff, 1753-1828 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kirms, Franz, 1750-1826 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Kleist, Heinrich von, 1777-1811 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Klettenberg, Susanna Katharina, 1723-1784 (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Klinger, Friedrich Maximilian von, 1752-1831 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Klinger - Family (Box 7, Folder +)
    - Klopstock, Friedrich Gottlieb, 1724-1803 (Box 7, Folder ++)
    - Knebel, Karl Ludwig von, 1744-1834 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Knebel - Family (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kniep, Christoph, 1748-1825 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Knortz, Karl, 1841- (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Koch, Frau Christiane Henriette Merleck (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Koch, Christoph Wilhelm, 1737-1813 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Koch, Heinrich Gottfried, 1703-1775 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Körner, Christian Gottfried, 1756-1831 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Körner, Theodor, 1791-1813 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Körner - Family (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Koethe, Frau Silvie Ziegesar, 1785-1850 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kolbe, Heinrich Christoph, 1771-1836 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kotzebue, August Friedrich Ferdinand von, 1761-1819 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Kräuter, Friedr. Theod. David, 1790-1856 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kraus, Georg Melchior, 1737-1806 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kreuchauff, Franz Wilhelm, 1727-1803 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Krüger, Georg Wilhelm, 1791-1841 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kügelgen, Gerhard von, 1772-1820 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kügelen - Family (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kühn (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kummerfeld, Frau Katharina Caroline Pauline Franzisca Schulze, 1745-1815 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Kurland, Anna Charlotte Dorothea, Herzogin von, 1761-1821 (Box 8, Folder +)
  - "L"
    - Lamartine, Alphonse Marie Louis de, 1790-1869 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - La Roche, Carl, 1794-1884 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - La Roche, Frau Sophie von, 1731-1807 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Lavater, Johann Caspar, 1741-1801 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Lavater, Lugwig, 1527-1586 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Leisewitz, Johann Anton, 1752-1806 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Le Kain, Henri Louis Cain, known as, 1728-1778 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lengefeld, Frau Luise Juliane Eleonore Friederike von Wurmb von, 1743-1823 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lenz, Jakob Michael Reinhold, 1751-1792 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lenz, Johann Georg, 1748-1832 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Leopold III, Duke of Anhalt-Dessau, 1740-1817 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Leopold, Maximilian Julius, duke of Brunswick-Lüneberg, 1752-1785 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lessing, Gotthold Ephraim, 1729-1781 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Levetzow - Family (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lichtenberg, Georg Christoph, 1748-1799 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lieber, Karl Wilhem, 1791-1871 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Liechtenstein, Joseph Wenzel Lorenz, Fürst von, 1696-1772 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Liechtenstein, Moritz Joseph Fürst von, 1775-1819 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Ligne, Charles Joseph, prince de, 1735-1814 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Lindenau, Bernhard August von, 1779-1854 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lobe, Johann Christian, 1797-1881 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lobstein, Johann Friedrich, 1736-1784 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1807-1882 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Louis Bonaparte, King of Holland, 1778-1846 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Louis Ferdinand, Prince of Prussia, 1772-1806 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Louise Auguste, Grand Duchess of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1757-1830 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Luden, Heinrich, 1780-1847 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Ludwig I, Grand Duke of Hesse-Darmstadt, 1753-1830 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Ludwig I, King of Bavaria, 1786-1868 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Ludwig VIII, Landgrave of Hesse-Darmstadt, 1691-1768 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Ludwig, Christian Gottlieb, 1709-1773 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Ludwig, Emil (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lüttwitz, Henriette Freiin von (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Luise, Queen Consort of Frederick William III, King of Prussia, 1776-1810 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Luise Eleonore, Duchess of Sexe-Meiningen, 1763-1837 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Luise Henriette Wilhelmine, Duchess of Anhalt, 1750-1811 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Luxembourg, Francois Henri de Montmorency, duc de, 1628-1695 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Lyncker, Larl Wilhelm Heinrich, Freiherr von, 1767-1843 (Box 8, Folder +)
  - "M"
    - Maass, Wilhelmine (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Manso, Johann Caspar, Friedrich, 1760-1826 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Manzoni, Alessandro, 1785-1873 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Mara, Frau Gertrud Elisabeth Schmeling, 1749-1833 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Marcard, Heinrich Mathias, 1750-1793 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Marchand, Frau Magdalena Brochard (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Marchand, Theobald, 1741-1800 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Maria Ludovica Beatrix Antonie Josephine, Empress Consort of Franz I, Emperor of Austria, 1787-1816 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Maria Luise Alexandrine, Princess of Prussia, 1808-1877 (Box 8, Folder ++)
    - Marie Louise Albertine, Reichsgräfin von Leiningen-Heidesheim, 1729-1818 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Mariia Pavlovna, Grand Duchess of Saxe-Wiemar-Eisenach, 1786-1859 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Mattei, Karl, 1744-1830 (Box 8, Folder +)
    - Matthison, Friedrich von, 1761-1831 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Maximilian I, Joseph, King of Bavaria, 1756-1825 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Maximilian, Friedrich (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Meiners, Christoph, 1747-1810 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Melchior, Johann Peter, 1742-1825 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Mendelssohn, Moses, 1729-1786 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix i.e. Jacob Ludwig Felix, 1809-1847 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Merck, Johann Heinrich, 1741-1791 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Merck - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Mérimée, Prosper, 1803-1870 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Metternich-Winneburg, Clemens Lothar Wenzel, Fürst von, 1773-1859 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Meyer von Knonau (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Meyer, Hans Heinrich, 1760-1832 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Meyer, Nicolaus, 1775-1855 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Meyerheim, Friedrich Eduard, 1808-1879 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Michaelis, Johann David, 1717-1791 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Mickiewicz, Adam, 1798-1855 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Miller, Johann Martin, 1750-1814 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Moltke, Karl Melchior Jakob, 1763-1831 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Moritz, Karl Philipp, 1757-1793 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Morus, Samuel Friedrich Nathanael, 1736-1792 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Moser, Friedrich Carl, Freiherr von, 1723-1798 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Mounier, Jean Joseph, 1758-1806 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Müller, August Eberhard, 1767-1817 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Müller, Carl Wilhelm, 1728-1801 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Müller, Friedrich, 1749-1825 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Müller, Friedrich von, 1779-1849 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Müller, Johannes von, 1752-1809 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Müllner, Amadeus Gottfried Adolf, 1774-1829 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Musäus, Johann Karl August, 1735-1787 (Box 9, Folder +)
  - "N"
    - Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1769-1821 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Nicolai, Christoph Friedrich, 1733-1811 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Nicolovius, Georg Heinrich Ludwig, 1767-1839 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Nicolovius - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Niebuhr, Barthold Georg, 1776-1831 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Niemeyer, August Hermann, 1754-1828 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Nothnagel, Johann Andreas Benjamin, 1729-1804 (Box 9, Folder +)
  - "O"
    - Oberkirch, Henriette Louise von Waldner Baronne d', 1754-1804 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Oberlin, Jeremias Jakob, 1735-1806 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Obermann (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Ochsenstein, Heinrich Christoph, 1715-1773 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - O'Donell, Josephine Gräfin von Gaisruck Gräfin von, 1779-1833 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Oehlenschläger, Adam Gottlob, 1779-1850 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Oelhafen, Tobias (Box 9, Folder +++)
    - Oels, Carl Ludwig, 1780-1833 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Oeser, Adam Friedrich, 1717-1799 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Oeser - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Oken, Lorenz, 1779-1851 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Olenschlager, Johann Daniel von, 1711-1778 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Orléans, Hélène Louise Elisabeth, duchesse d', 1814-1858 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Orth, Johann Philipp, 1698-1783 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Ott, Johann Kasper, 1740-1799 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Ott - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
  - "P"
    - Palladio, Andrea (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Paoli, Pascal de (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Pappenheim, Friedrich Ferdinand, Graf zu, 1702-1793 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Paulus, Heinrich Eberhard Gottlob, 1761-1851 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Pfeil, Johann Gottlob Benjamin, 1732-1800 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Philippine Charlotte, Duchess of Braunschweig-Wolfenbüttel, 1716-1801 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Pius VI, Pope, 1717-1799 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Planck, Gottlieb Jakob, 1752-1833 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Plotho, Erich Christopher, 1707-1788 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Preller, Friedrich Johann Christian Ernst, 1804-1878 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Pütter, Johann Stephan, 1725-1807 (Box 9, Folder +)
  - "R"
    - Racknitz, Joseph Friedrich, Freiherr von, 1744-1818 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Radziwill, Anton Hienrich, Fürst von, 1775-1833 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Ramler, Karl Wilhelm, 1725-1798 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Raphael, Alice Pearl, 1887- (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Raynal, Guillaume Thomas François, 1713-1796 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Rauch, Christian Daniel, 1777-1857 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Recke, Elisa von der (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reden, Friedrich Wilhelm, Graf von, 1752-1815 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Rehberg, Friedrich, 1758-1835 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reich - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reichard, Heinrich August Ottokar, 1751-1828 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reichardt, Johann Friedrich, 1752-1814 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Reichardt - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reiffenstein, Johann Friedrich, 1719-1793 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reil, Johann Christian, 1759-1813 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reinhard, Karl Friedrich, Graf von, 1761-1837 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reinhold, Karl Leonhard, 1758-1823 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reitenberg, Karl Kasper, 1774-1860 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Reuss, Jeremias David, 1750-1837 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Richter, August Gottlieb, 1742-1812 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Richter, Johann Paul Friedrich, 1763-1825 (Box 9, Folder ++)
    - Riemer, Friedrich Wilhelm, 1774-1845 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Riemer - Family (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Riese, Johann Jakob, 1746-1827 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Rietschel, Ernst Friedrich August, 1804-1861 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Robinson, Henry Crabb 1775-1867 (Box 9, Folder +)
    - Rochlitz, Friedrich Johann, 1769-1842 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Rodde, Frau Dorothea Schlözer von, 1770-1825 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Rodde, Matthäus (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Röhr, Johann Friedrich, 1777-1848 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Rösel, Johann Gottlob Samuel, 1769-1843 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Rollett, Hermann, 1819-1904 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Rousseau, Jean Baptiste, 1670-1741 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Runde, Justus Friedrich, 1741-1807 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Runge, Philipp Otto, 1777-1810 (Box 10, Folder +)
  - "S"
    - Sammet, Johann Gottfried, 1719-1796 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Sand, Karl Ludwig, 1795-1820 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Saussure, Horace Bénédict de, 1740-1799 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Savigny, Friedrich Karl von, 1779-1861 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Savigny, Frau Maria Kunigunde Brentano von, 1780-1863 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Savoie, Marie-Josephine-Louise de, comtesse de Provence, 1753-1810 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach. Post-Goethezeit personalities (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schadow, Johann Gottfried, 1764-1850 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schardt - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schellimg, Karoline Michaelis, 1763-1809 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schelling, Friedrich Wilhelm Joseph von, 1775-1854 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Scherbius, Johann Jacob Gottlieb, 1728-1804 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Scherr, Johannes, 1817-1886 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schiller, Frau Charlotte von Lengefeld von, 1766-1826 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schiller, Friedrich Wilhelm Ernst, 1796-1841 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich von, 1759-1805 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schiller (Group) (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich von, 1759-1805 (Box 10, Folder +++++)
    - Schiller, Karl Friedrich Ludwig, 1793-1857 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schiller, Nanette, 1777-1796 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schiller - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schiller im Bild (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlegel, August Wilhelm von, 1767-1845 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schlegel, Friedrich von, 1772-1829 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlegel, Johann Adolf, 1721-1793 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlitz, Genannt von Görtz, Johann Eustach, Graf von, 1737-1821 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schlözer, August Ludwig von, 1735-1809 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schlosser, Frau Cornelie Friederike Christine Goethe, 1750-1777 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlosser - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlosser, Hieronymus Peter, 1735-1797 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schlosser, Johann Georg, 1739-1799 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schmeller, Johann Joseph, 1796-1841 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schmid, Christian Heinrich, 1746-1800 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schmiedel - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schmoll, Georg Friedrich, -1785 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schöpflin, Johann Daniel, 1694-1771 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schopenhauer, Johanna, 1766-1838 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schopenhauer - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schröder, Friedrich Ludwig, 1744-1816 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schroeter, Corona Elisabeth Wilhelmine, 1751-1802 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schubart, Christian Friedrich Daniel, 1739-1791 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schuchardt, Johann Christian, 1799-1870 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schuckmann, Kaspar Friedrich von, 1755-1834 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schütz, Christian Georg, 1718-1791 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schütz, Johann Heinrich Friedrich, 1779-1829 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schütz, Frau Johanna Henriette Rosine Schüler, 1772-1849 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schulthess, Frau Anna Barbara Wolf, 1745-1818 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Schultz, Christoph Ludwig Friedrich, 1781-1834 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schulz, Johann Christoph Friedrich, 1747-1806 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schuler, Frau Charitas Meixner, 1750-1777 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schweighäuser, Johann, 1742-1830 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schweitzer, Albert, 1875- (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Schweitzer, Anton Theodor Heinrich, 1735-1787 (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Scott, Sir Walter, Bart., 1771-1832 (Box 10, Folder ++)
    - Seckendorff von - Family (Box 10, Folder +)
    - Seekatz, Johann Konrad, 1719-1768 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Seidler, Louise, 1786-1866 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Senckenberg, Johann Christian, 1707-1772 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Seyler, Frau Sophie Friederike Wilhelmine, Sparmann, 1738-1789 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Shaliapin, Fedor Ivanovich, 1873- (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Shelley, Percy Bysshe, 1792-1822 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Smith, Charlotte Turner, Mrs., 1749-1806 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Soemmerring, Samuel Thomas von, 1755-1830 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Sonnenberg, Franz Anton, Freiherr von, 1779-1805 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Sontag, Henriette, 1806-1854 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Soret, Frédéric, Jacob, 1795-1865 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Spalding, Johann Joachim, 1714-1804 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Spaur, Franz Joseph, Graf von, 1725-1797 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Speck, William Alfred, 1864-1928 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Spiegel, von und zu Pickelsheim, Karl Emil, Freiherr (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Sprengel, Kurt Polycarp Joachim, 1766-1833 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Sprickmann, Anton Matthias, 1749-1833 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Staël-Holstein, Anne Louise Germaine Necker, baronne de, 1766-1817 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Starck, Johann Jakob, 1730- (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stark, Johann Christian, d.Ä., 1753-1811 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Starck, Johann Jakob, 1730-1796 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stein, Frau Amalie Constantine Luise Henriette von Seebach von (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stein, Frau Charlotte Albertine Ernestine von, 1742-1827 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stein - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Sternberg, Kaspar, Graf, 1761-1838 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stith, Mrs. Catherine Potter, 1795-1839 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stock - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stolberg, Christian, Graf zu, 1748-1821 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stolberg, Friedrich Leopold, Graf zu, 1750-1819 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stolberg - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Stolz, Johann Jakob, 1754-1821 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Strecker, Wilhelm, 1795-1856 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Strohmeyer, Karl, 1780-1844 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Sulzer, Johann Georg, 1720-1779 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Suvorov, Aleksandr Vasilévich, kniaz Italiiski, 1729-1800 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Szymanowska, Mme. Maria Wolowska, 1795-1831 (Box 11, Folder +)
  - "T"
    - Talleyrand-Périgord, Charles Maurice de, Prince de Bénévent, 1754-1838 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Talma, François Joseph, 1763-1826 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Talva, Frau Charlotte Vanhove, 1771-1860 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Tasso, Torquato, 1544-1595 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Taylor, Bayard, 1825-1878 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Textor, Frau Anna Margaretha Lindheimer, 1711-1783 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Textor, Johann Wolfgang, 1638-1701 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Textor, Johann Wolfgang, 1693-1771 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Thoranc, François de Théas, comte de, 1719-1794 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Thümmel, Moritz August von, 1738-1817 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Thym, Johann Heinrich, 1723-1789 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Ticknor, George, 1791-1871 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Tieck, Friedrich, 1775-1851 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Tieck, Johann Ludwig, 1773-1853 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Tieck - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Tischbein, Johann Heinrich Wilhelm, 1751-1829 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Tobler, Johannes (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Trautmann, Johann Georg, 1713-1769 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Trautmann - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Trebra, Friedrich Wilhelm Heinrich von, 1740-1819 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Trippel, Alexander, 1744-1793 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Türckheim, Anna Elisabeth Schönemann Freifrau von, 1758-1817 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Türckheim - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
  - "U"
    - Urban, Mme. (Box 11, Folder +)
  - "V"
    - Varnhagen von Ense, Rahel Antonie Friederike (Levin), 1771-1833 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Vaudreuil, Gräfin Louise von (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Veit, Philipp, 1793-1877 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Veit - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Verschaffelt, Peter Anton von, 1710-1793 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Vogel, Carl, 1798-1864 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Voigt, Christian Gottlob von, 1743-1819 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Voigt, Friedrich Siegmind, 1781-1850 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Volckmann, Johann Jakob, 1732-1803 (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Voss, Heinrich, 1779-1822 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Voss, Johann Heinrich, 1751-1826 (Box 11, Folder ++)
    - Voss - Family (Box 11, Folder +)
    - Vulpius, Christian August, 1762-1827 (Box 11, Folder +)
  - "W"
    - Wagner, Heinrich Leopold (Box 11, Folder +)